Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.20
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio, 1976-1993; XX.
  - Governor, 1979-1987; 3.
    - Pennsylvania Distinguished Service Medal Presentation to General Matthew Ridgeway; introduction by General Richard M. Schott, Pennsylvania's Secretary of Military Affairs and remarks by Governor Thornburgh and General Ridgeway, Harrisburg [online], June 6, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 160)
    - Speech to the PA Department of Labor and Industry's Statewide Private Industry Council Conference, Harrisburg, June 10, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 161)
    - WPVI-TV Interview, Harrisburg, June 11, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 162)
    - Senate Bill 10 Bill Signing, Harrisburg, June 18, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 163)
    - Former Massachusetts Governor Dukakis' Testimony on Welfare Bill, Harrisburg, July 2, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 164)
    - PA Tourism Jingle by Agency C, July 3, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 165)
    - Press Conference, Harrisburg, July 29, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 167)
    - WPEN-AM/WMGK-FM Interview of Ginny Thornburgh with Deb Hamilton, August 30, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 168)
    - Lottery and Grand Jury Press Conference with Attorney General Bartle, Harrisburg, September 19, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 169)
    - Annual Gridiron Show, September 21, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 170)
    - Speech to the Polish Cultural Club Kosciuszko/ Pulaski Day Dinner, Mount Carmel and Lehigh University Commencement and Founder's Day Ceremonies, Bethlehem, October 10, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 171)
    - PA Transportation Service & Progress for the 80's Conference, State College, November 7, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 172)
    - Swearing-In Ceremony for Michael L. Browne as Insurance Commissioner, Harrisburg, November 12, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 173)
    - John Travolta and "Blow Out" Movie Cast Press Conference, Philadelphia, November 13, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 174)
    - Speech to the Republican Governors' National Policy Forum, Philadelphia, November 16, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 175)
    - National Republican Governors' Conference, November 17, 1980; 3 audiocassettes. (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 176 178)
    - National Republican Governors' Conference, November 18, 1980; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 179 180)
    - Press Conference, Philadelphia, November 18, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 181)
    - Seltzer Comments on Governor Thornburgh, November 25, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 182)
    - Law and Order Package Press Conference and Bill Signings, Philadelphia, December 4, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 183)
    - Clair & Chuck Renaissance Singers "Parkway Paranoia", 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 184)
    - "You've got a friend in Pennsylvania," Public Service Announcement, Montgomery County, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 185)
    - PA Tourism Music by Ketchum MacCleod & Grove, Inc, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 186)
    - "You've got a friend in Pennsylvania," Song (Two Versions), 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 187)
    - PA Tourism "Philadelphia Style" Song, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 188)
    - PA Tourism "Friend" Advertisement, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 189)
    - Starobin Remarks on Thornburgh's Tourism Campaign "You've Got a Friend in Pennsylvania," Harrisburg, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 190)
    - Pre-Budget Press Conference, Harrisburg, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 191)
    - Speech to the Joint Session of the General Assembly, Harrisburg, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 192)
    - "We're Growing Better," Speech at the PA Farm Show Opening Day Ceremonies, Harrisburg, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 193)
    - Associated Press Mid-Term Interview, Harrisburg, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 194)
    - United Press International Mid-Term Interview, Harrisburg, January 12, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 195)
    - Speech at the Dedication Ceremonies for Veterans Outreach and Assistance Center, Harrisburg, January 12, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 196)
    - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Commemorative Service, Harrisburg [online], January 14, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 197)
    - Service of Thanksgiving and Praise for Release of Hostages, Harrisburg, January 22, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 198)
    - Liquor Control Board Reform Press Conference, Harrisburg, January 28, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 199)
    - Regulatory Reform Press Conference with Senator Henry Hager, Harrisburg, January 29, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 200)
    - Budget Press Conference, Harrisburg, February 3, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 201)
    - Budget Address, Harrisburg, February 4, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 202)
    - Once a Year State Inspection Press Conference, Harrisburg, February 11, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 203)
    - Speech to the Golden Triangle Association's 29th Anniversary Luncheon, Pittsburgh, February 11, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 204)
    - Report on Community and Economic Development, Washington, D.C., February 21, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 205)
    - Announcement of Glen-Gary Corp. Re-Opening Plants in PA, Harrisburg, March 2, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 206)
    - Housing Press Conference, Harrisburg, March 5, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 207)
    - PA State Educator's Association Press Conference, Harrisburg, March 16, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 208)
    - PA Tax Commission Press Conference, Harrisburg, March 19, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 209)
    - Speech to the Johnstown Chamber of Commerce, March 19, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 210)
    - Speech to the PA White House Conference on Aging, Hershey, March 23, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 211)
    - Liquor Control Board Announcement Press Conference, Pittsburgh, March 24, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 212)
    - Centralia Mine Fire Press Conference, Centralia, March 31, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 213)
    - Southeastern PA Transit Authority Press Conference, Philadelphia, April 2, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 214)
    - Speeches to the Tennessee Cabinet and Staff, Nashville, and to the 59th Annual Convention PA State Association of Township Supervisors, Pittsburgh, April 4, 1981 and April 6, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 215)
    - Retreat State Hospital Press Conference, Wilkes-Barre/Scranton, April 8, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 216)
    - Rail Policy Press Conference, Altoona, April 9, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 217)
    - Arnold Palmer "Tour Stop" Business Breakfast Press Conference, Coraopolis, and Report of Tax Commission, April 13, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 218)
    - Speech to the Shenango Valley Urban League, Inc. 13th Annual Banquet, West Middlesex, April 20, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 219)
    - Speech at the Erie Insurance Group Groundbreaking Ceremony, Erie and American Sterilizer Company Press Conference and Tour, Erie, April 20, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 220)
    - Anti Crime Package Press Conference with District Attorney Edward Rendell, Philadelphia, April 21, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 221)
    - Taiwan Purchase Contract Signing, and Holocaust Proclamation Signing, Harrisburg, May 1, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 222)
    - Susquehanna Sound "Animal Crackers" with Ginny Thornburgh and Charlie, May 4, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 223)
    - Hazlett Memorial Awards for Excellence in the Arts in PA Presentation to James Michener, Harrisburg, May 5, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 224)
    - Coalition of NE Governors (CONEG) Meeting, Philadelphia, May 7, 1981; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 225 226)
    - "Project Harvest" Press Conference with Secretary of Aging Gordon Black, Harrisburg and Tax Commission Report, May 27, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 227)
    - Water Initiative Legislation (Bond Issue) Press Conference, Harrisburg, June 1, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 228)
    - Speech to PA AFL-CIO, Philadelphia, June 2, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 229)
    - H.B 1291 Welfare Deficiency Bill Signing, Harrisburg, June 10, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 230)
    - Speech to Career Inc., Operation Dig with Nate Smith, Pittsburgh [online], June 13, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 231)
    - Press conference with Dr. Harold Wilke, Pittsburgh, June 19, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 232)
    - Harrisburg Fire Symposium, Harrisburg, June 22, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 233)
    - SB 161 and H.B 712 Bill Signing, Harrisburg, June 23, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 234)
    - Ginny Thornburgh at SCI Capitol Hill, June 23, 1981 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 235)
    - Speech to the Department of PA Veterans of Foreign Wars, Harrisburg, June 25, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 236)
    - SB 422 and H.B 143 Bill Signing, Harrisburg, June 30, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 237)
    - Speech to the PA American Legion 63rd Annual Department Convention, Pittsburgh, July 11, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 238)
    - Labor and Industry Press Conference with Secretary Charles Leiberth, Harrisburg, July 15, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 239)
    - Edison Electric Press conference, Kansas City, MO, September 10, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 240)
    - Prison and Sentencing Legislation Press Conference, Harrisburg, September 16, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 241)
    - Annual Gridiron Show, September 21, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 242)
    - Handicapped Awareness and Employment of the Handicapped Week Proclamation and Project Pelion Flag Presentation, September 21, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 243)
    - Speech to the 1981 Governor's Occupational Safety and Health Conference, Camp Hill, September 23, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 244)
    - School Strike Press Conference, Philadelphia, October 1, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 245)
    - Energy Press Conference, Harrisburg, October 6, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 246)
    - 2100 Employee High Tech Expansion Commodore Intl., Ltd. Press Conference, Norristown, October 7, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 247)
    - Press Conference with President Reagan, Philadelphia, October 15, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 248)
    - Swearing-in ceremony; Secretary Cliff Jones, October 19, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 249)
    - Speech to the PA State Conference of the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, Erie, October 23, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 250)
    - Speech to the 109th Annual Session All-Grange Banquet, Altoona, October 27, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 251)
    - Graterford Prison Press Briefings on release of hostages, November 2, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 252)
    - Remarks and Bill Signing of H.B 357 to the PA Farmers' Association, Hershey, November 9, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 253)
    - Senior Citizen's Lottery Press Conference, Philadelphia, November 10, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 254)
    - Crime Package Meeting with Philadelphia Police Officials, Philadelphia, November 17, 1981 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 255)
    - United Press International: Three Years as Governor Interview, Harrisburg, December 16, 1981; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 256 257)
    - Associated Press: Three Years as Governor Interview, Harrisburg, December 22, 1981; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 258 259)
    - Philadelphia Bulletin Interview, Harrisburg, January 6, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 260)
    - POW License Plate Presentation, Harrisburg, January 7, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 261)
    - ABC Nightline Interview with Ted Koppel, Harrisburg, January 26, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 262)
    - Southeastern PA Transportation Authority Press Conference, Philadelphia, February 5, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 263)
    - Budget Address, Harrisburg, February 9, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 264)
    - Budget Press Conference, McKees Rocks, PA, February 11, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 265)
    - Endorsement of Philadelphia Labor Leaders Press Conference, Philadelphia, February 25, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 266)
    - Department of Community Affairs Check Presentation for the Harrisburg Train Station Renovation, Harrisburg, March 29, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 268)
    - Passage of Welfare Bill Interview with Sandy Starobin, March 31, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 269)
    - Speech to the Associated PA Constructors 61st Annual Luncheon Meeting, Atlantic City, NJ, March 31, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 270)
    - Early Retirement for Teachers and Municipal Liquid Fuels Tax Check Deliveries Press Conference, Philadelphia, April 2, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 271)
    - H.B 720 Welfare Reform Bill Signing, Harrisburg, April 8, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 272)
    - H.B 720 Welfare Reform Bill Press Conference, Harrisburg, April 8, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 273)
    - Greensburg Tribune Review Interview regarding Welfare Reform, Harrisburg, April 8, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 274)
    - Gypsy Moth Press Conference, Harrisburg, April 12, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 275)
    - Tourism Press Conference, Harrisburg, April 13, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 276)
    - PA Housing Finance Agency Press Conference, Harrisburg, April 15, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 277)
    - "The Pennsylvania Lawyer" Magazine Interview, Harrisburg, April 19, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 278)
    - Erie I-79 Groundbreaking; H.B 1575 Agent Orange Bill Signing, Wilkes-Barre, April 28, 1982 April 29, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 279)
    - Speech and Governor's Export Awards Presentation to the 7th Annual Keystone Dinner Pennsylvania International Trade Conference, Hershey, May 3, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 280)
    - Fairchild Weston PA Industrial Development Association Loan Announcement and Press Conference, Scranton, May 5, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 281)
    - New Era Local Tax Reform Interview, May 9, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 282)
    - Budget SB 929 General Fund, H.B 517 Education Funding, SB 1300 Special Funding Bill Signings, Harrisburg, May 11, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 283)
    - "Tougher Laws for Drunk Drivers" Press Conference, June 3, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 285)
    - Speech to the PA American Automotive Association Federation, Hershey, June 30, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 286)
    - Energy Council Conference, July 14, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 287)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Centers Press Conference with Rev. Leon H. Sullivan, Philadelphia, July 20, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 288)
    - Route 220/22 Construction Press Conference, Altoona, July 28, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 289)
    - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees Press Conference, Philadelphia, August 2, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 290)
    - Tourism and Presentation of Pennsylvania's Distinguished Service Medal to General Edward C. Meyer, Harrisburg, September 3, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 291)
    - 1982 Governor's Occupational Health & Safety Conference, Camp Hill, September 15, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 292)
    - Annual Gridiron Show, September 21, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 293)
    - Press Conference, Philadelphia, September 23, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 294)
    - "PA Economy Magazine" Interview, Harrisburg, September 24, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 295)
    - Wall Street Journal Interview, Review of First Term Issues and Accomplishments, Harrisburg [online], October 5, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 296)
    - Hahnemann Medical College and Hospital Press Conference regarding PA Industrial Development Association (PIDA) Business and Shared Medical, Philadelphia, October 6, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 297)
    - Mellon Institute Press Conference regarding PA Industrial Development Association (PIDA) Loan to Industrial Development Corp., Pittsburgh, October 8, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 298)
    - Philadelphia Daily News Interview, Harrisburg, October 13, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 299)
    - PA School Boards Association, Inc.'s Presentation of "Outstanding Service to Education," Hershey, October 13, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 300)
    - USA Today Interview; Harrisburg, November 29, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 303)
    - H.B 2046 Public Employees' Pension, H.B 50 Good Samaritan Bill, H.B 353 Local Health Department Employees, Bill Signings, Harrisburg, December 1, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 304)
    - CBS News Radio "What's Happening" Telephone Interview, Harrisburg, December 2, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 305)
    - Hershey Medical Center, Harrisburg; HB 2344 "Ben Franklin Partnership" Bill Signing, Harrisburg, December 6, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 306)
    - H.B 2533 Driving Under the Influence Bill Signing, Hershey, December 15, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 307)
    - A: Interview with VJT re Christmas; B: Pittsburgh Press Interview, Harrisburg, with Governor, December 16, 1982 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 308)
    - Budget Reviews Hearing Press Conference, Harrisburg, January 3, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 309)
    - 1983 PA Farm Show, Harrisburg, January 9, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 310)
    - Inauguration Address, Harrisburg, January 18, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 311)
    - Budget Address, Harrisburg, February 8, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 312)
    - Budget Press Conference, Harrisburg, February 8, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 313)
    - Hospital Cost Containment Press Conference, Harrisburg, March 25, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 314)
    - Introduction of President Reagan at the National Conference on Dislocated Workers, Pittsburgh, April 6, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 315)
    - Jay Waldman's Testimony regarding the General Counsel's Budget, April 7, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 316)
    - Unemployment Compensation Bailout Press Conference, Harrisburg, April 19, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 317)
    - Health Care for the Unemployed Press Conference, Pittsburgh, April 19, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 318)
    - Bi-annual Fire Awareness Symposium, Camp Hill, April 22, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 319)
    - Grand Opening Ceremonies of the State Street Office Building, Harrisburg, April 22, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 320)
    - Ginny Thornburgh's Mother's Day Speech, Valley Forge Military Academy [online], May 8, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 321)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Centers Press Conference, Washington, D.C., June 6, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 322)
    - SB 5 Odometer Regulations Bill Signing, Harrisburg and Budget Press Conference, Harrisburg, June 14, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 323)
    - Chesapeake Bay Press Conference, Harrisburg, June 20, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 324)
    - SB 527 Budget Bill Press Conference, Harrisburg, July 11, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 325)
    - Unemployed Compensation Bill Signing, Harrisburg, July 21, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 326)
    - Corrections Press Announcement, Camp Hill, September 21, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 327)
    - Annual Gridiron Show- with Governor Thornburgh (master), September 21, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 328)
    - Speech at the Veterans Leaders/Medal of Honor Recipient Ceremonies, Harrisburg, September 26, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 329)
    - Judicial Reform Press Conference, Camp Hill, October 3, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 330)
    - 5th National Conference on States and Small Business, Minneapolis, MN, October 13, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 331)
    - Education Announcement: Pennsylvania Department of Education, Pittsburgh, October 17, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 332)
    - Memorial Service for Servicemen Killed in Beirut, Lebanon, Wormleysburg, PA, October 29, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 333)
    - Avian Influenza Press Conference, November 1, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 334)
    - Liquor Control Board Press Conference, Pittsburgh, November 29, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 335)
    - Governor's Toll Roads Task Force, Harrisburg, December 21, 1983 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 336)
    - WQXA Radio (York) Telephone Interview, Harrisburg, January 6, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 337)
    - Liquor Control Board Reform Press Conference, Pittsburgh, January 24, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 338)
    - Liquor Control Board Press Conference, Erie and Budget Address, Harrisburg, February 3, 1984 and February 7, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 339)
    - Budget Press Conference, Harrisburg, February 7, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 340)
    - Speech to the Pennsylvania Environmental Conference, March 2, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 341)
    - Student Loan Announcement Press Conference with the PA Higher Education Authority Act, Harrisburg, March 26, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 342)
    - Economic Bond Issue Press Conference, Harrisburg, April 4, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 343)
    - "You've got a friend in Pennsylvania" and the "Philadelphia song" written & recorded by Marty Portnoy (leading Philadelphia Society Orchestra), April 17, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 344)
    - Press Conference and Photo Hour, April 24, 1984 (Box 1605, Cassette DTA 345)
    - Safe Water Bill Signing, Harrisburg, May 1, 1984 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 346)
    - "Assignment Small Business" National Federation of Independent Business, PA Public Service Announcement, May 7, 1984; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 347 348)
    - Distinguished PA Artist Award Presentation to Bill Cosby, Harrisburg, May 8, 1984 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 349)
    - Annual Press Gridiron Show: Thornburgh's Monologue [online], September 21, 1984 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 350)
    - Associated Press Steve Liddick interviews Ginny Thornburgh, November 26, 1984 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 351)
    - Annual Gridiron Show - Governor Thornburgh & Lieutenant Governor Scranton (master), September 21, 1985 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 352)
    - Conversations: "America's Industrial Future", Hilton Head, August 24, 1986 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 353)
    - Annual Gridiron Show- Governor Thornburgh, September 21, 1986 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 354)
    - USIA Sao-Paulo, Brazil, telephone conference regarding Economic Development, September 18, 1986 and September 23, 1986 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 355)
    - Thornburgh Narrates "Peter and the Wolf" with the Harrisburg Symphony Orchestra, Harrisburg, December 10, 1986 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 356)
    - Child Abuse Public Service Announcements, undated (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 357)
    - Children's Health Insurance Program (CHIP) Public Service Announcement, undated (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 358)
    - Liquor Control Board Public Service Announcement, undated (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 359)
    - Mine Subsidence Insurance Public Service Announcement, undated (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 360)
    - OPINA Act Public Service Announcement, undated (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 361)
    - Scranton's Visitors and Convention Bureau Autumn Travel Ads, undated (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 362)
  - Reelection Campaign for Governor, 1982; 4.
    - Re-election Campaign Press Announcement, Johnstown [online], March 3, 1982 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 267)
    - Re-election Campaign Press Conference with Lieutenant Governor Scranton, Pittsburgh, May 24, 1982 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 284)
    - Election Night Comments by Jay Waldman and Governor Thornburgh, Philadelphia [online], November 2, 1982 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 301)
    - Post re-election Campaign Press Conference, Philadelphia [online], November 3, 1982 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 302)
  - Three Mile Island (TMI), 1979-1999; 5.
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Emergency Press Conference (1st), March 28, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 363)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Briefing, Wednesday Evening, March 28, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 364)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Briefing, 10 PM, March 28, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 365)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Conference (with Thornburgh), March 29, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 366)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Conference, March 30, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 367)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Conference, Saturday Night; Harold Denton and Governor Thornburgh [online], March 31, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 368)